A Guide to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Yucca Mountain Research Collection TD898.12.N3 U85
University of Nevada, Reno. DeLaMare Science & Engineering Library
- Heatherton, T.F., Kleck, R.E., Hebl, M.R. et al. "The social psychology of stigma." (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Desert Research Institute. "Branch technical procedures field archaeology." (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Dublyansky, Y. "Secondary mineral assemblages in fractures and lithophysal cavities at Yucca Mountain Nevada, USA [presentation abstract]." (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Dunne, G.C. "Geologic evolution of the southern Inyo Range, Darwin Plateau, and Argus and Slate Ranges, East-Central California-an overview." (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Earle, T.C. and Cvetkovich, G. "Determining the determinants of trust." From Risk Analysis. (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Easterling, D. "The vulnerability of the Nevada visitor economy to a repository at Yucca Mountain." From Risk Analysis. (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Flynn, J. Slovic, P. and Kunreuther, H. "Risk, media and stigma." (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Elkins, N.Z. "[Exploratory studies facility test program evaluation of activities and impacts related to tunnel boring machine excavation of the bow ridge fault and associated tunnel zone. Memorandum to S.B. Jones, et al. (Department of Energy)]." Los Alamos National Laboratory. (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Environmental News Network. "Gore makes 47 commitments to sustainability." (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Kerrisk, J.F. "Reaction-path calculations of groundwater chemistry and mineral formation at Rainier Mesa, Nevada." Los Alamos National Laboratory. (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Travis, B.J., Hodson, S.W., Nuttall, H. E. et al. "Preliminary estimates of water flow and radionuclide transport in Yucca Mountain." Los Alamos National Laboratory., undated (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Caporuscio, F.A. and Vaniman, D.T. "Iron and manganese in oxide minerals and in glasses: Preliminary consideration of Eh buffering potential at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Los Alamos National Laboratory. (Box 111, Folder 14)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Motor vehicle-related air toxics study." EPA 420-R-93-005. (Box 112, Folder 1)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Molybdenum CASRN 7439-98-7." (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Fleck, R.J. "Tectonic style, magnitude, and age of deformation in the sevier orogenic belt in Southern Nevada and Eastern California." From Geological Society of America Bulletin. (Box 112, Folder 3)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Cancer risk coefficients for environmental exposure to radionuclides." EPA 402-99-001. (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Fleck, R.J., Turrin, B.D., Sawyer, D.A. et al. "Age and character of basaltic rocks of the Yucca Mountain region, Southern Nevada." From Journal of Geophysical Research. (Box 112, Folder 5)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Chapter 13.2.1: Paved roads." From AP-42, 5th edition. (Box 112, Folder 6)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Boron (boron and borates only); CARSN 7440-42-8." (Box 112, Folder 7)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Cadmium; CASRN 7440-43-9." (Box 112, Folder 8)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Chromium(VI); CASRN 18540-29-9." (Box 112, Folder 9)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Manganese; CASRN 7439-96-5." (Box 112, Folder 10)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Nickel, soluble salts, CASRN various." (Box 112, Folder 11)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Zinc and compounds; CASRN 7440-66-6." (Box 112, Folder 12)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Peak air quality statistics for the six principal pollutants by metropolitan statistical area." (Box 112, Folder 13)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Heavy duty engine and vehicle standards and highway diesel fuel sulfur control requirements." EPA 420-F-00-057. (Box 113, Folder 1)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "State detailed analysis, the national biennial RCRA hazardous waste report." EPA 530-R-01011. (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Estrada, M. "Draft final environmental impact statement for the F-22 Air Force development evaluation [document removed]." (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Ettlin, D.M. "Burning cars in rail tunnel resist control; crews use manhole to approach blaze with cooling water 'like walking into an oven' 5 of 60 cars removed." From The Baltimore Sun. (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Fabryka-Martin, J.T., Flint, A.L., Sweetkind, D.S. et al. "Evaluation of flow and transport models of Yucca Mountain, based on chlorine-36 studies for FY97." Los Alamos National Laboratory. LA-CST-TIP-97-010. (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Fillmore, D. "[DOE-EM group 12 heat generation rate in the YM EIS appendix A. Email communication to J. Linhart, DOE-EM]." INEL. (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Federal Emergency Management Agency. "Guidance for developing state, tribal, and local radiological emergency response planning and preparedness for transportation accidents." FEMA REP-5, Rev. 02. (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Finley, N.C., Aldrich, D.C., Daniel, S.L. et al. "Transportation of radionuclide in urban environs [document removed]." (Box 113, Folder 8)
- Slovic, P. "The perception of risk." (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Flint, L.E. "Characterization of hydrogeologic units using matrix properties, Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Water-resources investigations report 97-4243. (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Flynn, T. Buchanan, P., Trexler, L. et al. "Geothermal resource assessment of the Yucca Mountain Area, Nye County, Nevada - final report." University and Community College System of Nevada. BA0000000-03255-5705-00002. (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Flynn, J.H., Mertz, C.K., and Slovic, P. "Results of a 1997 national nuclear waste transportation survey." Decision Research. (Box 114, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Transportation. "Safety compliance oversight plan for rail transportation of high-level radioactive waste and spent nuclear fuel, ensuring the safe, routine rail transportation of foreign research reactor spent nuclear fuel." (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Freeze, G. "[EIS post-10,000 year FEP's. Email communication with D. Lester, Jason Technologies]." (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Los Alamos National Laboratories. "Pinon pine tree study, Los Alamos National Laboratory: Source document." LA-13693-MS. (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Fridrich, C.J. "Tectonic evolution of the Crater Flat Basin, Yucca Mountain region, Nevada." From Cenozoic Basins of the Death Valley Region. (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Friertag, J. "Frenald not too neighborly for home values." From Journal News. (Box 114, Folder 8)
- Gamble, H.B. and Downing, R.H. "Effects of nuclear power plants on residential property values." From Journal of Regional Science. (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Gamble, H.B., Downing, R.H. and Sauerlender, O.H. "Community of growth around nuclear power plants." From Journal of the American Real Estate and Urban Economics Association. (Box 114, Folder 10)
- Gawande, K. and Jenkins-Smith, H. "Nuclear waste transport and residential property values: Estimating the effects of perceived risks." From Journal of Environmental Economics and Management. (Box 114, Folder 11)
- Gertz, C. "Programmatic agreement among the United States Department of Energy (DOE), the Advisory Council on Historic Preservation (council), and the Nevada State Historic Preservation Officer (SHPO) for the first nuclear waste deep geologic repository program Yucca Mountain, Nevada." (Box 114, Folder 12)
- Gibson, R.H. ed. "Pocket guide for sanitarians and engineers 1974 [document removed]." (Box 114, Folder 13)
- Glancy, P.A. and Beck, D.A. "Modern flooding and runoff of the Amargosa River, Nevada-California, emphasizing contributions of Fortymile wash." From Quaternary Geology of the Yucca Mountain Area. Friends of the Pleistocene. (Box 114, Folder 14)
- Golder Associates. "Software code: RIP [document removed]." (Box 114, Folder 15)
- Gonzales, D. "[Request for information: Dose to subsurface workers in the ESF. Email communication to T. Ikenberry]." (Box 114, Folder 16)
- Greenberg, M.R. and Williams, B. "Geographical dimensions and correlates of trust." From Risk Analysis. (Box 114, Folder 17)
- Grendstad, G. and Selle, P. "Cultural myths of human and physical nature: Integrated or separated?" From Risk Analysis. (Box 114, Folder 18)
- Griego, N.R., Smith, J.D. and Neuhauser, K.S. "Investigation of radtran stop model input parameters for truck stops." Sandia National Laboratories. SAND96-0714C. (Box 114, Folder 19)
- Guida, R.A. "[Size and weight limits for canisters used for disposal of naval spent nuclear fuel. Letter to Dr. R. Dyer, DOE]." Department of the Navy. (Box 114, Folder 20)
- Gunter, G. "[Actual land disturbance calculations for rail corridors. Telephone communication to S. Kelderhouse, BSC]." Tetra-Tech NUS. (Box 114, Folder 21)
- Hall, E.J. "Radiolobiology for the radiologist [document removed]." (Box 114, Folder 22)
- Hamann, J.E., Klein, D.E., Pope, R.B. et al. "Modeling of pool fire environments using experimental results of a two-hour test of a rail/cask system [document removed]." (Box 114, Folder 23)
- Haschke, J.M., Allen, T.H., and Morales, L.A. "Reaction of plutonium dioxide with water: formation and properties of PuO2+x." From Science. (Box 114, Folder 24)
- Harris Miller Miller & Hanson. "Transit noise and vibration impact assessment." (Box 114, Folder 25)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste types and amounts from highway construction. Telephone communication to M. Elicuquey, Nevada DOT]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste types and amounts from highway construction. Telephone communication to D. James, Nevada DOT]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste types and amounts from highway construction. Telephone communication to S. Oxoby, Nevada DOT]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste types and annual quantities from GSA fleet operations at the Savannah River Site (SRS). Telephone communication to R. Baker, GSA]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste types and quantities expected from minor repair and routine maintenance of 20 tractor trailers. Telephone communication to S. Kelly, Bechtel Nevada]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste generated during the construction and maintenance of a rail line. Telephone communication to L. Cerny, Association of American Railroads]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste generated during routine maintenance of rail cars. Telephone communication to B. Vliek, Thrall Car Manufacturing]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Hoganson, M. "[Waste generated during the maintenance of rail line stationary equipment and rolling stock (while in operation). Telephone communication to L. Cerny, Association of American Railroads]." Tetra Tech NUS. (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Holdren, J.P., Ahearne, J.F., Budnitz, R.J., et al. "Management and disposition of excess weapons plutonium, rector-related options [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Holmes & Narver, Inc. "Soils investigation for Sandia Laboratories NNWSI Area 25 Nevada Test Site." Report #ES 133. (Box 115, Folder 10)
- Horn, J.M., Davis, M. Martin, S. et al. "Assessing microbiologically induced corrosion of waste package materials in the Yucca Mountain repository." Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory. URCL-JC-130567. (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Huerta, M. "Analysis, scale modeling, and full scale tests of a truck spent-nuclear-fuel shipping system in high velocity impacts against a rigid barrier [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Huerta, M. "Analysis, scale modeling, and full scale tests of a railcar and spent-nuclear-fuel shipping cask in a high velocity impact against a rigid barrier [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Huerta, M. and Yoshimura, H.R. "A study and full-scale test of a high-velocity grade-crossing simulated accident of a locomotive and a nuclear-spent-fuel shipping cask [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 14)
- International Commission on Radiological Protection. "Limits for intakes of radionuclides by workers [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 15)
- International Commission on Radiological Protection. "Limits for intakes of radionuclides by workers [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 16)
- International Commission on Radiological Protection. "Age-dependent doses to members of the public from intake of radionuclides [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 17)
- Ikenberry, T. "[Radon diffusion and effect of concrete liners on radon flux. Telephone communication to Y. Yuan, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System]." Jason/Dade Moeller & Associates. (Box 115, Folder 18)
- Ikenberry, T.A. "Determining representative characteristics of commercial spent nuclear fuel assemblies for accident analyses in the Yucca Mountain final environmental impact statement." DMA-TR-01. Dade Moeller & Associates, Inc. (Box 115, Folder 19)
- Intertech Consultants and Sweetwater Consulting Services. "Alamo land use plan." (Box 115, Folder 20)
- Idaho National Engineering and Environmental Laboratory. "CD-design basis event data (DBE)." National Spent Nuclear Fuel Program. Revision 1. (Box 115, Folder 21)
- Idaho National Engineering Laboratory. "Fort St. Vrain independent spent fuel storage installation safety analysis report." Docket no. 72-09, revision 2. (Box 115, Folder 22)
- Institute of Medicine, National Research Council. "Exposure of the American people to iodine-131 from Nevada nuclear-bomb tests." (Box 115, Folder 23)
- Interagency Review Group on Nuclear Waste Management. "Report to the president by the Interagency Review Group on Nuclear Waste Management." (Box 115, Folder 24)
- Jacobs, W. "[Area 25 facilities NTS. Email communication to G. Gunter, BSC]." Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. (Box 115, Folder 25)
- Jason Technologies Corporation. "Reference cost report for continued storage." Revision 01. (Box 115, Folder 26)
- Jason Technologies Corporation. "An evaluation of the consequences of a commercial aircraft crash into the Yucca Mountain Repository, final draft [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 27)
- Jefferson, R.M. and Yoshimura, H.R. "Crash testing of nuclear fuel shipping containers [document removed]." (Box 115, Folder 28)
- Johnson, P.E. and Michelhaugh, R.D. "Transportation routing analysis geographic information system (WebTRAGIS) user's manual." Oak Ridge National Laboratory. ORNL/TM-2000/86. (Box 115, Folder 29)
- Karagiannis, H. and Hagemeyer, D.A. "Occupational radiation exposure at commercial nuclear power reactors and other facilities." U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. NUREG-0173, Vol. 21. (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Kasperson, R.E., Ren, O, Slovic, P. et al. "The social amplification of risk: A conceptual framework." From Risk Analysis. (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Keck, T.J. "Record of decision for the United States Air Force F-22 force development evaluation and weapons school [document removed]." (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Kilroy, K.C. "Ground-water conditions in Amargosa Desert, Nevada-California, 1952-1987: Water-resources investigations report 89-4101." U.S. Geological Survey. (Box 116, Folder 4)
- King, M.J. and Bredehoeft, J.D. "Death Valley Springs geochemical investigation Yucca Mountain Nuclear Repository, Inyo County oversight-1998." The Hydrodynamics Group. (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Knop, M. "[Transportation issue .eps files. Email communication to L. Hall, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System]." (Box 116, Folder 6)
- Kraus, S.J. "Attitudes and the prediction of behavior: A meta-analysis of the empirical literature." From Personality and Social Psychology Bulletin. (Box 116, Folder 7)
- Lacziniak, R.J., DeMeo, G.A., Reiner, S.R., et al. "Estimates of ground-water discharge as determined from measurements of evapotranspiration, Ash Meadows area, Nye County, Nevada: Water-resources investigation report 99-4079." U.S. Geological Survey. (Box 116, Folder 8)
- Lander County, Nevada. "Revised policy plan for federally administered lands." (Box 116, Folder 9)
- Lane, F. "[Revised engineering files, retrieval table for construction. Email communication to K. House, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System.]." (Box 116, Folder 10)
- Langford, I.H., Georgiou, S., Bateman, I.J. et al. "Public perceptions of health risks from polluted coastal bathing waters: A mixed methodological analysis using cultural theory." From Risk Analysis. (Box 116, Folder 11)
- Lehman, L.L. and Brown, T.P. "Summary of state of Nevada-funded studies of the saturated zone at Yucca Mountain, Nevada performed by L. Lehman." L. Lehman & Associates, Inc. (Box 116, Folder 12)
- LeCain, G.D., Anna, L.O. and Fahy, M.F. "Results from geothermal logging, air and core-water chemistry sampling, air-injection testing, and tracer testing in the Northern Ghost Dance Fault, Yucca Mountain, Nevada, November 1996 to August 1998 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- Levich, R.A., Linden, R.M., Patterson R.L. et al. "Hydrologic and geologic characteristics of the Yucca Mountain site relevant to the performance of a potential repository." From Great Basin and Sierra Nevada: Field Guide 2. (Box 116, Folder 14)
- Levy, L.E. "[Population estimates through the third quarter, 1996, Nye County, Nevada. Memorandum to L. Bradshaw, Nye County Nuclear Waste Repository Program]." Planning Information Corporation. (Box 116, Folder 15)
- Long, J. and Fischhoff, B. "Setting risk priorities: A formal model." From Risk Analysis. (Box 116, Folder 16)
- Barke, R., Espey, J. and Jenkins-Smith, H. "The evolution of policy contexts: Analyzing the bases for change in mass perceptions of nuclear politics." (Box 116, Folder 17)
- Petterson, J.S. "Remedying fundamental flaws in the Nation's Civilian Radioactive Waste Management Program." (Box 116, Folder 18)
- U.S. Government Accountability Office. "Yucca Mountain Project: Information on estimated costs to respond to employee e-mails that raised questions about quality assurance." (Box 116, Folder 19)
- U.S. Government Accountability Office. "Yucca Mountain: DOE has improved its quality assurance program, but whether its application for a NRC license will be high quality is unclear." (Box 116, Folder 20)
- State of Nevada, Office of the Governor, Agency for Nuclear Projects. "State of Nevada comments on the U.S. Department of Energy's draft environmental impact statement for a geologic repository for the disposal of spent nuclear fuel and high-level radioactive waste at Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada." Volume 1. (Box 117, Folder 1)
- State of Nevada, Office of the Governor, Agency for Nuclear Projects. "State of Nevada comments on the U.S. Department of Energy's draft environmental impact statement for a geologic repository for the disposal of spent nuclear fuel and high-level radioactive waste at Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada." Volume 2. (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Luna, R. "Comparison of results from two spent fuel sabotage source term experiments [document removed]." (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Marks, S.L. "[First report on results from geodetic monitoring of the Yucca Mountain region using continuous GPS measurements - task 1. Letter to R. James, DOE]." University of Nevada, Las Vegas. (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Marris, C., Langford, I.H. and O'Riordan, T. "A quantitative test of the cultural theory of risk perceptions: Comparison with the psychometric paradigm." From Risk Assessment. (Box 117, Folder 5)
- McCann, E.W. "[Summary of waste management activities by the Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project (YMP) for calendar year 1999. Letter to S.A. Wade, DOE/YMSCO]." Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. (Box 117, Folder 6)
- McClelland, L.F., Keller, J.T., Keller, G.P. et al. "Guidelines for evaluating and documenting rural historic landscapes." From National Register Bulletin 30., undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
- McCullum, R. "[DOE request for updated information on reactor site cask handling capacity. Letter to J. Booth, DOE/YMSCO]." Nuclear Energy Institute. (Box 117, Folder 8)
- McKenzie, J.M. "[Response to request for the NNPP (Naval Nuclear Propulsion Program) to submit information on a variety of topics. Letter to J.R. Dyer, DOE/YMSCO]." Department of the Navy. (Box 117, Folder 9)
- Medical Center Online. "Search results for Las Vegas, NV with radius of <100 mile(s)>." (Box 117, Folder 10)
- Harris, C.M. "Handbook of acoustical measurements and noise control." (Box 118, Folder 1)
- U.S. Geological Survey. "Seismotectonic framework and characterization of faulting at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Ch. 1-3. (Box 119, Folder 1)
- U.S. Geological Survey. "Seismotectonic framework and characterization of faulting at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Ch. 4-5. (Box 119, Folder 2)
- U.S. Geological Survey. "Seismotectonic framework and characterization of faulting at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Ch. 6-8. (Box 119, Folder 3)
- U.S. Geological Survey. "Seismotectonic framework and characterization of faulting at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Ch. 9-11. (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Metz, W.C. and Clark, D.E. "The effect of decisions about spent nuclear fuel storage on residential property values." From Risk Assessment. (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Miller, C.D., Mullineaux, D.R., Crandell, D.R. et al. "Potential hazards from future volcanic eruptions in the Long-Valley Mono Lake area, East-Central California and Southwest Nevada - a preliminary assessment." U.S. Geological Survey. Geological survey circular 877. (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Mishra, S. "[Importance analysis. Email to D. Lester, Jason Technologies]." Civilian Waste Management System. (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Moeller, D.W. "Environmental health: Revised edition." (Box 120, Folder 4)
- Mon, K. "[Importance analysis. Email communication to S. Mishra, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System]." Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Monette, D.D. "[Nevada test site (NTS)/Yucca Mountain project (YMP) airspace incursion counts. Letter to J.R. Dyer, DOE]." Department of Energy. (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Montazer, P. and Wilson, W.E. "Conceptual hydrologic model of flow in the unsaturated zone, Yucca Mountain, Nevada: Water-resources investigations report 84-4345." U.S. Geological Survey. (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Morissette, R. "[Aircraft counts. Email communication to P. Davis, Jason Technologies]." Department of Energy. (Box 120, Folder 8)
- Morissette, R. "[Traffic count. Email communication to P. Davis, Jason Technologies]." Department of Energy. (Box 120, Folder 9)
- Morissette, R. "[Commercial engine shaft info. Email communication to P. Davis, Jason Technologies]." Department of Energy. (Box 120, Folder 10)
- Morissette, R. "[NTS air traffic counts for 3rd quarter. Email communication to P. Davis, Jason Technologies]." Department of Energy. (Box 120, Folder 11)
- Morton, D. "[Supplement below-boiling scenarios." Email communication to T. Ikenberry, Dade Moeller and Associates et al.]." (Box 120, Folder 12)
- Murphy, B.D. "Characteristics of spent fuel from plutonium disposition reactors vol. 3: a Westinghouse pressurized-water reactor design." Oak Ridge National Laboratory. ORNL/TM-13170/V3. (Box 120, Folder 13)
- Murphy, S. L. "Deaths: Final data for 1998." From National Vital Statistics Reports. (Box 120, Folder 14)
- Nakayachi, K. "How do people evaluate risk reduction when they are told zero risk is impossible?" From Risk Analysis. (Box 120, Folder 15)
- Napier, B.A., Peloquin, R.A., Strenge, D.L. et al. "Hanford environmental dosimetry upgrade project: GENII - the Hanford environmental radiation dosimetry software system. Volume 1: Conceptual representation." Pacific Northwest Laboratory. PNL-6584. (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Napier, B.A., Peloquin, R.A., Strenge, D.L. et al. "Hanford environmental dosimetry upgrade project: GENII - the Hanford environmental radiation dosimetry software system. Volume 2: User's Manual." Pacific Northwest Laboratory. PNL-6584. (Box 121, Folder 2)